cl.ly 2016-03-30

# CloudApp - Privacy

We at CloudApp recognize that you expect privacy and security when it comes to information that personally identifies you and allows you to be individually contacted ("Personal Information"). We adopted the following online privacy policy because we understand the need to safeguard the information you may be providing to us at our websites. 

### Why we request information about you

CloudApp collects and retains Personal Information about you only when you have communicated with us by email (we'll collect your email address), when you register to use CloudApp's services (we'll ask for your name and email address), and when you register for paid services (we'll ask for general information such as your name, email address, billing address, and credit card information). 

We use that information to transact business with you and deliver requested services from time to time, as well as services improvement, contact, and research. 

### How we protect your information

The information we receive from you is protected against unauthorized access once we receive it. We limit the access to your information to employees who have a business reason for accessing it. When collecting financial information from you, we use secure socket layer software (SSL). 

Despite our continual and evolving efforts to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Information. You acknowledge and agree that we make no such guarantee. 

### Data Storage

CloudPlus uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run CloudApp. Although CloudPlus owns the code, databases, and all rights to the CloudApp application, you retain all rights to your data. 

### About our cookies

We do use cookies. 

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer hard drive. We use cookies so our web site can remember you and provide content you're most likely to request. We also use cookies to gather statistical information about our web site, such as the time users spend at a site and the pages they visit most often. Those statistics do not contain Personal Information. We will also use cookies for advertising and remarketing purposes. 

Links to other web sites 

Our web sites may contain links to and from other web sites. Some links may be in the form of display advertising. We cannot guarantee that web sites other than our websites will respect and protect your Personal Information like we do. For your own protection, you should go to and read the privacy statements/policies of other web sites when you visit them. 

We are not responsible for the content of websites other than our web sites. 

### Your consent

When you provide us with Personal Information, you consent to the collection and use of this information by CloudApp. 

### Disclosure

We will not sell or distribute your Personal Information except to provide products or services you have requested, when we have permission, or it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law. 

Business transfers 

If CloudApp, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, Personal Information would be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of CloudApp may continue to use the Personal Information as set forth in this policy. 

### Data Integrity

CloudApp processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage, and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store, and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

### Safe Harbor Framework

CloudApp adheres to the U.S., EU, and Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks which are administered by the U.S. Department of Commerce. We comply with the Safe Harbor privacy principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access and Enforcement. Details on the frameworks are found at: <http://export.gov/safeharbor/>. 

### Enforcement

Enforcement – Customer Service is staffed to assist and support our customers’ activities and accounts, and also to enforce adherence to our User Agreement terms and conditions. Customer Service can suspend and/or terminate service for any account for breach of those terms or operating in a manner inconsistent with the terms of service. CloudApp’s Human Resources department also works closely with department heads to ensure policies are adhered to and when necessary to terminate employment for any employee, permanent or temporary, that breaches the terms of hire, or presents a security risk. 

CloudApp regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or CloudApp's treatment of personal information by contacting us through this web site or by writing to us at Your Privacy Rights, c/o CloudApp, PO Box 29502 #96560, Las Vegas, NV 89126-9502. When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is CloudApp's policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between CloudApp and an individual. 

European residents with inquiries regarding data privacy can contact us at the above address or at privacy@getcloudapp.com. If, after contacting us, you believe your data privacy inquiry has not been resolved to your satisfaction, you may contact the Direct Marketing Association at:

Safe Harbor  
Direct Marketing Association  
1615 L St. NW, Ste 1100  
Washington, DC 20036-5624  
<https://thedma.org/consumer-guide/>

### Amendments

We may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your CloudApp primary account holder account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

Questions on our privacy policy can be directed to [support@getcloudapp.com](mailto:support@getcloudapp.com).
